

Product & Web Designer

I am a product and web designer with 10+ years of experience. I worked in teams on high-impact, large projects for brands like Ford, Deutsche Telekom, Graphisoft, and Samsung. I helped win 3 creative awards (and support wildlife) with a sustainable website.

Budapest, Hungary +36 20 617 6328 gergo.zambo.designer@gmail.com gergozambo.com linkedin.com/in/gergozambo

Experience

Product (UX/UI) Designer Ergomania (2023-present)

- Leading cross-platform mobile app design projects for British fintech startups to help them focus on user needs and go to market
- · Redesigning identities and websites of international brands
- · Conducting competitor analysis, interviews, and user research
- Managing the internal AI research and design team to innovate and improve design workflows

VML

Senior Digital (ux/u1) Designer (2021-2023)

- · Designed mobile apps, websites, and games for digital promotions
- · Developed and utilized design systems of global brands
- · Led copywriters and designers to develop creative concepts
- Won 3 creative awards for designing a sustainable website that helped raise awareness of water pollution

Digital (ux/ui) Designer (2019-2021)

- Took part in day-long branding workshops for startups and global companies, helping them create their brand's core ideas
- Redesigned a global tech company's brand identity and website, repositioned it as a unique player in its market space

Graphic & Web Designer Tricky (2017-2019)

 Designed user flows, UI kits, and developer handoffs for music streaming platforms, generated lots of uploads and high traffic

Graphic & Web Designer Freelance (2016-2017)

- · Led redesign and design projects for corporate & state organizations
- Conducted thorough ${\tt UX}$ audit and research of large webshops

Art Director & Editor-in-Chief ELTE (2014-2016)

Junior Front-End Developer Mito (2013)

Web Design Intern Everengine (2012)

Tools

- · Figma, FigJam, Miro
- · Notion, ClickUp, Slack
- · Adobe Ps, Ai, Id, XD, Acrobat
- · Midjourney, ChatGPT

Skills

- · Wireframing, prototyping
- UI design, design systems
- · Brand identity, typography
- User tests, interviews, workshops
- · Competitor analysis
- ux & website audits
- HTML, CSS, WCAG, SEO
- Generative AI
- · Project & stakeholder management

Recommendations

"Gergő listens, absorbs, and delivers thoughtful and beautifully executed designs." Robin Smith, Creative Director at The Hanging House

"Gergő has a friendly, professional, no-nonsense attitude, insightful questions, and a desire to understand what we want to achieve."

Péter Balla, Technical Director at centropa.org

Education, training

Product (UX/UI) Designer MOME (2020)

Design Theory MA MOME (2017-2019)

Linguistics & Literature BA ELTE (2013-2016)

Languages

- English (C1, Full professional proficiency)
- · Hungarian (Native)

For more about my experiences, awards, and projects, please see my LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/gergozambo

